John Bell Hatcher Archives
Yale Peabody Museum of Natural History
John Bell Hatcher Archives
1884-1892
VPAR.000255
Yale Peabody Museum of Natural History
5
various boxes
The archives of John Bell Hatcher notably including specimen lists, notebooks (personal and field), correspondence and some biographical materials. All relate to his time at Yale.
Hatcher, John Bell, 10/11/1861-07/03/1904
Biographical Sketch
Hatcher was made Curator of Paleontology and Osteology at the Carnegie Museum in Pittsburgh.
Description of the Material
The archives of John Bell Hatcher are from his time collecting at Yale (1884-1892) include notebooks (personal and field), correspondence and some biographical materials.
Field notebooks; Correspondence; Locality information; Yale Peabody Museum; Yale University
- Biographical Materials, 1884-1890; Series I
  - Biographical Materials., 002750
- Correspondence, 1887; Series II
  - Correspondence., 002751
- Field Notes, 1884-1892; Series III
  - Field Notes., 1884-1889; 000259
  - Field Notes., 1890-1892; 000260
- Specimen Lists, 1884-1892; Series IV
  - Specimen Lists., 1884-1889; 000262
  - Specimen Lists., 1890-1892; 000263